Guide to the Carla Stellweg Papers M1752
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Carla Stellweg papers
1935-2015
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stellweg, Carla
M1752
60 Linear Feet (122 boxes)
The Carla Stellweg papers document Stellweg's curatorial work, writing, and other professional activities. Materials include exhibition catalogs, correspondence, publications, photographic materials, and administrative records.
Arrangement
The collection is arranged in ten series:
Series 1. Artists Series 2. Gallery Shows, Curatorial Work and Other Professional Activities Series 3. Frida Kahlo Exhibits Series 4. Articles, Reviews, and Other Writing Series 5. Publications Series 6. Personal and Biographical Information Series 7. Photographic Materials Series 8. Audiovisual Materials Series 9. Financial Records (Restricted) Series 10. Accession 2015-145. Additional Materials
Acquisition Information
This collection was purchased by Stanford University, Special Collections in 2010 and 2015. Accessions 2010-095 and 2015-145.
Scope and Content of Collection
The Carla Stellweg papers document Stellweg's curatorial work, writing, and other professional activities. Materials include exhibition catalogs, correspondence, publications, photographic materials, audiovisual materials and administrative records.
Accession 2015-145 includes photographs, slides, papers, journals, cassettes, and one hard drive.
Biography
Carla Stellweg is a curator, art historian, and writer who specializes in the promotion of Latin American art and artists. Born in Bandung, Indonesia, she moved to Mexico with her family in the late 1950s, where she lived and worked for twenty-five years. Stellweg received a Bachelor of Arts from Grotius College and was a Master of Fine Arts Candidate in art history at the University of the Americas, Mexico. Stellweg held a variety of curatorial and management positions throughout her career. She was the founder and editor of Artes Visuales, which was the first Spanish and English contemporary visual arts magazine published in Latin America. In 1979, Stellweg became the deputy director of the newly built Rufino Tamayo Museum. From 1983-1985, Stellweg was the director of the Stellweg-Seguy Gallery, managing exhibitions and sales. She became the chief curator of the Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art (MOCHA) in 1986, where she worked on exhibits such as Rooted Visions: Mexican Art Today. In 1989, she became the owner and director of her own gallery in New York City. The Carla Stellweg Gallery's mission was to promote emerging and mid-career artists, as well as to provide a gallery space for diverse exhibitions. Stellweg also worked as the executive director of Blue Star Art Space and as the director of program funding for the Jewish Museum, where she was in charge of an annual campaign to raise more than 3 million dollars. In 2005, Stellweg became an art history professor at the School of Visual Arts. In addition to these positions, Stellweg worked as an independent consultant on various projects, including Hispanic Art in the United States: Thirty Contemporary Painters and Sculptors and The Latin American Spirit: Art and Artists in the US, 1920-1970. Stellweg was a co-author of The Camera Seduced: Portraits of Frida Kahlo, a book which arose out of her work on an exhibition of the same name. She received a Rockefeller Fellowship in the Humanities, with the research topic "Exhibiting Practices of Mexican and Chicano Art: Its Funding and Collecting."
Access to Collection
Open for research except for Series 9 (restricted financial records). Audio-visual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Art, Modern -- 20th century.; Art, Latin American.; Eleta, Sandra; Colo; Chong, Albert; Montes, Roberto Gil de; Rippey, Carla; Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz; Garaicoa, Carlos; Elizondo, Arturo; Venegas, Germán; Vater, Regina; Tamayo, Ruffino; Vargas, Eugenia; Suter, Gerardo; Camnitzer, Luis; Milton, Avery; Amado, Jesse; Kahlo, Frida; Stellweg, Carla; Carlos Capelán; Carla Stellweg Latin American & Contemporary Art (Gallery: New York, N.Y.); Peláez, Paloma; Parcero, Tatiana; Palacios, Jaime; Ortiz, Raphael Montanez.; Mendieta, Ana; Lozano, José; Lara, Magali; Lamelas, David; Labin, Clemencia; Jiménez, Cisco; Henning, Anton
- Series 1. Artists
  Scope and Content
  This series is divided into subseries by artist and arranged alphabetically by last name of artist. Materials include exhibit catalogs, correspondence, biographies of artists, slides, reviews, and price lists. Many of the individuals represented in this series were Carla Stellweg Gallery artists.
  - Jesse Amado
    - Jesse Amado (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Jesse Amado correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Jesse Amado press (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Jesse Amado price list receipts (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Jesse Amado (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - "Art Pace", 1995 Jan 15-Feb 26 (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Milton Avery
    - Milton Avery: press, background information (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Milton Avery: exhibit prep., 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Milton Avery: exhibit catalog (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Milton Avery Show: Caracas (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Santa Barraza
    - Santa Barraza press, 1983, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Santa Barraza (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Sanat Barraza correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Santa Barraza shipment delivery receipts, loan agreement form, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Luis Camnitzer
    - Luis Camnitzer bios and his texts (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Luis Camnitzer press, 1986-1996 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Luis Camnitzer correspondence, 1980-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Identidad, museo de arte moderno de Bogota (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Contemporary, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Luis Camnitzer (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Art Nexus (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ARTL!ES magazine, fall, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Artforum (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Art in America, Camnitzer publication, 1997 Mar (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Atlantica; revista de arte y pensamiento (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Slides, Prints, tec. Camnitzer (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Luis Camnitzer price lists, delivery receipts (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Luis Camnitzer (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Luis Camnitzer: exhibit catalogs (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Luis Camnitzer: exhibit catalogs (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Luis Camnitzer (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - Carlos Capelan
    - Carlos Capelan (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Carlos Capelan press biblio (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Carlos Capelan correspondence, 1991-1997 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Carlos Capelan slides (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Carlos Capelan exhibit catalogs (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - St. Clair Cemin, Jose Bedia, Carlos Capelan (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Carlos Capelan (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Carlos Capelan, exhibit catalog, 1994 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Carlos Capelan (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Carlos Capelan (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Carlos Capelan (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Carlos Capelan - Art in America press article, 1995 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Carlos Capelan - Karte Land Schaft Raummalerei (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Albert Chong
    - Albert Chong (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Albert Chong correspondence, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Albert Chong press, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Albert Chong price list (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Papo Colo
    - Photogenics [rare artist book] (Flat-box 93, Folder 2)
  - Esperanza Cortes
    - Esperanza Cortes (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Esperanza Cortes correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Esperanza Cortes press, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Esperanza Cortes price lists, loan agreement forms, receipts, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Sandra Eleta
    - Sandra Eleta (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Sandra Eleta correspondence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Sandra Eleta price lists, art work received/ receipt, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Arturo Elizondo
    - Arturo Elizondo (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Arturo Elizondo correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Arturo Elizondo press, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Arturo Elizondo invoices/price list, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Arturo Elizondo Latin American literature and arts/press article, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Arturo Elizondo: exhibit catalogs (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Arturo Elizondo: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Carlos Garaicoa
    - Carlos Garaicoa (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Carlos Garaicoa press, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Carlos Garaicoa Poliester press article, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Art Nexus, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Carlos Garaicoa consignment agreement, shipment receipts, loan agreement forms, 1994-1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Carlos Garaicoa correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Arturo Elrondo, Carlos Garaicoa (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Carlos Garaicoa: exhibit catalog (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Carlos Garaicoa: exhibit catalogs (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Margaret Garcia
    - Margaret Garcia correspondence, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Margaret Garcia press article/ magazine of the Los Angeles County Museum of Art, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Margaret Garcia press, 1986-1989 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Margaret Garcia (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Margaret Garcia artwork inventory list (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz
    - Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Nereyda Garcia- Ferraz loan consignment agreement, shipment receipts, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Nereyda Garcia-Ferraz: exhibit catalogs (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Robert Gil de Montes
    - Robert Gil de Montes (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Robert Gil de Montes (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Robert Gil de Montes correspondence, 1989-1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Robert Gil de Montes press, 1985-1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Robert Gil de Montes price lists, consignment price list, consignment receipts, delivery receipt, loan agreement forms, 1988-1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Robert Gil de Montes press, 1985-1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Robert Gil de Montes: exhibit catalogs (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Maria Elena Gonzalez
    - Maria Elena Gonzalez (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Maria Elena press materials, 1990-1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - M.E. Gonzalez correspondence, 1994-1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Maria E. Gonzalez price list invoices (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Maria Elena Gonzales: exhibit catalogs (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Luz M. Gordillo
    - Luz M. Gordillo (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Luz M. Gordillo press, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Luz M. Gordillo correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Luz M. Gordillo price lists, loan agreement form, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Anton Henning
    - Anton Henning (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Anton Henning correspondence, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Anton Henning press, 1992-1993 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Anton Henning consignment agreement forms, returned artwork receipt, price list, shipping receipt, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Anton Henning: exhibit catalogs (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Anton Henning: exhibit catalogs (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Anton Henning: exhibit catalogs (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Anton Henning, exhibit catalog, 1991 (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Cisco Jimenez
    - Cisco Jimenez (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Cisco Jimenez correspondence, 1994-1997 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Cisco Jimenez press, 1993-1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Cisco Jimenez plural (Bazaar magazine press articles), 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Art Nexus, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Cisco Jimenez receipts/price list, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Cisco Jimenez portfolio (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Darra Keeton
    - Darra Keeton (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Darra Keeton press, gallery release, 1991-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Darra Keeton operating budget exhibition breakdown, postcard invitation forms, artwork delivery receipt, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Darra Keeton: paintings, drawings" (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Clemencia Labin
    - Clemencia Labin (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Clemencia Labin press, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Clemencia Labin correspondence, 1996-1998 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Clemencia Labin price lists, artwork delivery receipt, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Clemencia Labin (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Clemencia Labin (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Clemencia Labin (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Clemencia Labin (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Clemencia Labin, catalogs (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - David Lamelas
    - Lamelas gallery, 1993-1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - David Lamelas press-biblio, 1972-1997 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Magali Lara
    - Magali Lara (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Magali Lara correspondence, 1989-1995 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Magali Lara press, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Magali Lara artwork receipts (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Magali Lara: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Magali Lara: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Magali Lara: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Magali Lara: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Magali Lara: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "Magali Lara", 2002 (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Jose Lozano
    - Jose Lozano (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Jose Lozano correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Jose Lozano press, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Jose Lozano exhibition loan agreement form, art loan agreement form, artwork sale receipt, delivery receipts, price lists, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ana Mendieta
    - Ana Mendieta (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Ana Mendieta correspondence, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Ana Mendieta press, 1982-2001 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Raquel Mendieta included living rites, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Ana Mendieta: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Rafael M. Ortiz
    - Rafael M. Ortiz [includes photographs] (Flat-box 96, Folder 2)
    - Rafael M. Ortiz: press, various texts (Flat-box 93, Folder 4)
  - Jaime Palacios
    - Jaime Palacios various press and invites and p.r. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - J.P press (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Jaime Palacios correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - J.P. Loan C. Hammer gallery chicago, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Loan forms, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - OMRS Hon. J. Palacios, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Jaime Palacios slides (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Jaime Palacios slides (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Jaime Palacios slides (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Jaime Palacios slides (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Plans show installation at CS gallery, 1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Art Nexus, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - J. Palacios Brussels show gallery CS Gallery, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Tatiana Parcero
    - Tatiana Parcero (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Tatiana Parcero: correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Tatiana Parcero: press, 1992-1997 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous art magazines (re. Tatiana Parcero) (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Tatiana Parcero: press/Harper's Bazaar/Mexico (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Tatiana Parcero: gallery docs/invoices/checklist (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Adolfo Patino
    - Adolfo Patino: press, 1978-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Adolfo Patino: loans agreement forms (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Adolfo Patino (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Paloma Pelaez
    - Paloma PeLaez: correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Paloma PeLaez: press, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Paloma PeLaez: shipment deliveries, loan agreement forms, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Paloma Pelaez: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Paloma Pelaez: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Carla Rippey
    - Carla Rippey (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Carla Rippey: correspondence, 1995- (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Carla Rippey: press, 1985- (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Carla Rippey: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Carla Rippey: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Carla Rippey: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Raimundo Rubio
    - Raimundo Rubio (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Raimundo Rubio: press, 1993- (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Raimundo Rubio: correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Raimundo Rubio: appraisal, price lists, receipts (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Raimundo Rubio: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Raimundo Rubio: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Raimundo Rubio: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Juan Sanchez
    - Juan Sanchez: CS/Gallery (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Juan Sanchez: press, 1985-1994 (Box 10, Folder 16)
    - Juan Sanchez: correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Juan Sanchez: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Juan Sanchez, et. al.: exhibit catalogs (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Gerardo Suter
    - Gerardo Suter (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Gerardo Suter: correspondence, 1992-1996 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Gerardo Suter: press, 1992-1995 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - "Into the Past," Eliot Weinberger (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Gerardo Suter publications (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Gerardo Suter publications (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Gerardo Suter publications (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Gerardo Suter: loan agreements, shipment receipts, invoices (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Gerardo Suter: "Cantos Rituales" (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Gerardo Suter: "Anahuac," "Codices" (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Gerardo Suter: "Traces" (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Gerardo Suter: "17 Artistas Mexicanos Contemporaneous" (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Gerardo Suter: "Labryinth of Memory" (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Gerardo Suter: "Tiempo Inscrito" (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Rufino Tamayo
    - Rufino Tamayo exhibit catalog (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Rufino Tamayo (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Rufino Tamayo (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Press (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - Rufino Tamayo exhibit catalog (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Tamayo (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Tamayo a modern icon reinterpreted (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Venezia Biennale, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Rufino Tamayo (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Rufino Tamayo (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Rufino Tamayo: Myth and Magic (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - [Rufino Tamayo] (Box 82, Folder 19)
    - [Rufino Tamayo - Correspondence] (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - [Rufino Tanayo Museum] (Flat-box 96, Folder 6)
  - Milagro de la Torre
    - Milagro de la Torre (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Milagro de la Torre: press, 1993-1996 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Milagro de la Torre: correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Milagro de la Torre: shipment, invoices, etc. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Milagros de la Torre (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Eugenia Vargas
    - Eugenia Vargas (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Eugenia Vargas: correspondence, 1993-1997 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Eugenia Vargas, 1988-1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Eugenia Vargas: Arte Internacional, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Eugenia Vargas: Atlantica, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Eugenia Vargas: miscellaneous articles (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Eugenia Vargas: Art Nexus (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Eugenia Vargas: Art in America (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Eugenia Vargas: gallery documents (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Eugenia Vargas: correspondence, articles (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Eugenia Vargas: "Through the Path of Echoes" (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Eugenia Vargas: "Companeras de Mexico" (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Regina Vater
    - Regina Vater (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Regina Vater: correspondence, 1989-1992 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Regina Vater (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - German Venegas
    - German Venegas (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - German Venegas: correspondence, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - German Venegas: press, 1985-1989 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - German Venegas: invoices (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Kukuli Velarde
    - Kukuli Velarde (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Kukuli Velarde: correspondence, 1990-1997 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Kukuli Velarde: slides (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Kukuli Velarde: prints (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Kukuli Velarde: prints, negatives (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Kukuli Velarde: proof sheets, negatives (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Kukuli Velarde: prints, negatives (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Kukuli Velarde: press, 1992-1995 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Kukuli Velarde: magazine articles (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Kukuli Velarde: loans, 1990-1995 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Kukuli Velarde: misc. catalogs (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous individual artists
    - Carlos Almaraz (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Margarita Becerra (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Maria Fernanda Cardoso (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Fernando Castro (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Enrique Castro-Cid (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Eduardo Costa (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Nicola Costantino (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Valdir Cruz (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Jamie Davidovich [includes photographs] (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Antonio Diaz (Flat-box 92, Folder 4)
    - Gonzalo Diaz (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Juan Douney (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Leon Ferrari (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Rafael Ferrer (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Mathias Goeritz/Jean Tinguely (Flat-box 93, Folder 3)
    - F. Colon Gonzalez (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Silvia Gruner (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Arturo Herrera (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Carlos Jurado (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Leandro Katz [includes photographs] (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Marisela LaGrave: exhibit catalogs (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Ricardo Lanzarini (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Julio le Parc (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Martin Lopez (Flat-box 92, Folder 2)
    - Pedro Lujan (Flat-box 96, Folder 7)
    - Fabian Marcaccio (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Enrique Martinez-Canas (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Diego Medina (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Cildo Meireles (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Catalina Mejia Perez (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Marta Minujin (Flat-box 96, Folder 1)
    - Liliana Porter (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Luis Felipe Noe (Flat-box 92, Folder 3)
    - Renata Pedrosa (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Miguel Rio Branco (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Angel Rodriguez-Diaz (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Miguel Angel Rojaz (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Doris Salcedo (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Nicholas Uribe (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Nathum Zenil (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Series 2. Gallery Shows, Curatorial Work and Other Professional Activities
  This series documents Stellweg's professional activities as a curator and director of various art galleries and museums, including her work at the Carla Stellweg Gallery, the Stellweg-Seguy Gallery, the Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art (MOCHA), the Rufino Tamayo Museum, Blue Star Art Space, and White Box. The series also documents Stellweg's professional consulting work and fundraising efforts. Materials include correspondence, documentation on artists and exhibitions, catalogs, exhibition invitations, appointment books, and administrative records. Information on Stellweg's involvement in exhibitions and projects such as Rooted Vision: Mexican Art Today, Soul Catchers, and The Latin American Spirit: Art and Artists’ Presence in the US, 1920-1970 can be found in this series.
  Many of these files have been kept in their original order with original folder headings.
  - Yearly appointment book, 2002 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Yearly appointment book, 2003 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Yearly appointment book, 2004 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Yearly appointment book, 2005 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Yearly appointment book, 2006 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Yearly appointment book, 2007 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Miscellaneous memo books, Undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous memo books, Undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Agenda book, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Unknown address book and 2 zip disks (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Unknown address book (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Yona Backer 2nd Day Market, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Expenses Reta Blo Show, 1990-1991 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Alice Rahon, 1990-1992 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Varo, Rahon: sales and legal, 1990-1994 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Botero secondary market, 1990-1994 (Box 39, Folder 8)